http://www.tron.co.uk/info/privacy/

We are committed to protecting your personal information and being transparent about what information we hold about you.
Using personal information allows us to develop a better understanding of our customers and in turn to provide you with relevant and timely information about the work that we do – both on and off stage.  As a registered charity, it also helps us to engage with potential donors and supporters.
The purpose of our policy is to give you a clear explanation about how we [and all of our subsidiaries] collect and use the information we collect from you directly and from third parties.
We use your information in accordance with all applicable laws concerning the protection of personal information.
If you wish to make changes to permissions you’ve gave when registering with one of our online systems, you can do so via your Theatre Account {https://www.tron.co.uk/secure/account/} or OpenTable Account {https://www.opentable.com/start/home}.
Our website may contain links to external websites managed and maintained by external companies. We cannot take any responsibility for content or privacy practices within these sites.
A full version of the privacy policy can be downloaded here as a word file or as a pdf.
Our privacy policy also appear on pages where we will collect information from you so you can easily refer back to it should you need to.
If you have any questions, please contact us:
Privacy Compliance
Tron Theatre
63 Trongate
Glasgow
G1 5HB
PrivacyCompliance@tron.co.uk
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
